Welcome to ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Welcome to ICICI Lombard General
Insurance.
Hello, welcome to I Lamb.  You are
talking to Lakhan.  What kind of
help can I provide?
Sir, I had got the policy removed.  I have
not received the policy policy from you.
Yes sir.
Ok.  Can you confirm your name
?
My name is Lalit.   My
name is Lalit.
Thank you.  Girl ji to confirm her name.
Do you have any policy number like proposal number etc. of the policy that you
renewed?
No, there is no proposal number.
He had renewed my RM.  I had made the
payment.
And I have called you many times.  So
he said it will be solved in 24 to 48 hours.  I did
not receive any call from your side.
So how will the phone be?
I am checking on line.
I am checking below on the G line.
Yes, if
I check now, the
request you made is still open,
it has not been closed yet.
No, it will remain open but you did not poll me, so
how many days have passed today?
Lagao, payment was made on 18th.  Today is the 5th,
so it has been 12, 15, 17, 18 days.
Yes, then
in how many days will you give it?  Meaning, is there a time limit like one month,
two months, six months?
I am checking the details,
what is the policy regarding that?
Yes check look check.
And as I can tell
you got a call from our priority team.   Did
not come.
Because I am able to check like that.  Like
our priority team is handling your case.
When they asked for the account
statement of the amount
debited, our team asked for that statement.
Look, the team is asking for a statement.
I have made payment to you also.  I
sent you the screenshot.  The statement of my payment is from
15th to 15th.  It is on
15th so I have
sent you the screenshot of the statement to customer
support anyway.  You check it once.   I
just mailed it to you, please WhatsApp me.
Ok.  Live on the line.
You paid ₹3152 for the screenshot you took.   Yes.
And he has mentioned the order ID and the
transaction ID done through the card like you have also mentioned.
Absolutely.
So your bill cycle will be generated as per your requirement only after 15th.   It is from
15 to 15.  When I downloaded it, it only
came till 15th because I made the payment on 18th.
Ok.   Yes.   Can
I put your call on hold for a minute or two
?
Absolutely.
Session
[Music]
hey session
hey session hey session
[Music]
hey session
hey sash
sashb
[Music]
sashb [Music]
hey session [Music]
hey sashba [
Music]
sashba
[Music]
hey sash
slowly
session
[Music]
health
sash
thank you for staying tuned sir
so ma'am you will get a call from our priority team
within two hours I have
mentioned to our priority team
your billing cycle statement is from
15th August to 15th September the
statement which is your billing cycle
so I mentioned this and you are able to
download the statement
no statement is coming at all
and the snapshot which you shared the
payment which you had made
yes yes so
our
priority team which is handling your case will
call you back within 2 hours
100%
that is fine sir but when I spoke to you
yesterday or the day before yesterday
they were saying 24 hours  I will call you
within 24 hours, but no call came from
them saying
ok but you will get 100% response within 2 hours, it does
not take 24 hours now because your
case is already being handled by the periodicity team.
No, I do
n't understand what I am saying here sir.
I have told you the payment time.  Everything was done
and your RM
generated that QR code for my payment.
Why don't you talk to your RM?
Who made my payment.  I did
not make the payment myself.  They have
generated the QR code.  I have made payment on that.
Tell me what to do in this?  I talk to his team.
They say it will happen today
, it will happen tomorrow, it will happen tomorrow.  Now tell me, there is
no coordination among you.  So if
you believe me, what claim will you get
passed?  What will happen to me?  I don't think so.
Your ICC service is so bad.  You
mean, if you are
not able to give me the policy then you will not pass the claim tomorrow.
You are sure of this.  This is a
matter of record.  You will see that you will
not even pass the claim.   Nothing like this can
happen to you.  A
policy is not being generated from you.  How
will you pass the claim?  Tell.
As I want to tell you,
our team is already working on the college.  He did
not handle the case I sent you, listen to me.  I don't know what the team is doing or not doing.  The
payment I have made is against your RM.
You have it working.
His name is Gautam ji.  You should talk to him.
He generated the QR code.  You have been
paid but still you are not
getting the payment.  Don't know what is happening.
Tell me how this can happen.  Or if I have made the online
payment myself then accept it brother, I have made a
mistake.  But your
RM has generated the QR code and
your payment has been made through it.
I have the screenshot.  Tell me how will you work?
Ok.  So I am mentioning him with regards.
Like team call, like you talked
to Gautam ji.  They generated and shared the QR code with you.
Yes, then talk to him.  I should deny
that the payment did not come or was not made.  He did this by
generating a QR code.  Tell me, it is such a
bad thing that I feel that
I have wasted at least 10 hours of your time by
calling you.  You don't mean that there is no
time.  You don't have the price.   All of
you say sorry, nothing will happen.  Keep
checking.   Still nothing will happen.
48 hours will also pass.  Even if
24 days pass, you will still get a
call in two hours. This is not our periodicity, this has been happening for the last
10 days.  100% of the time we get calls
but we can't do anything.
If you want, I can also share my employment.
Like you will get a call from
our periodic team.
No, the call will come but what will I do?
When nothing is happening to you.  So only they
can share all your details because the same
team is handling your case.
Okay, I can wait for 2 hours but
I know nothing is going to happen.  Ok.  Okay,
so 100% they will give you a recession.
Nothing will happen, I know.  You will have to
call again.  Nothing is going to happen.  Ok.
Ok.   He has
already mentioned everything.
As
you mentioned it, Sir, I have mentioned it four or five times
before also.  Nothing
happened to them.   Yes.   Still nothing happens.
I have full
confidence in ICC.  Nothing is ever going to happen.
Now this is my mistake.  I am
stuck here.  Will you please get my claim passed
?  Do I have a claim?  If
I need it tomorrow, I don't think the
claim will even be approved at your place.
This is my last one.  Right now I will never get it done in ICC.
And if my money was refunded, please refund it.
I will get it done by someone else.
Understood?  Please tell me two minutes.
If the money can be refunded then please refund my money.
I will get it done somewhere else, Max,
Bhupa or someone else, I am
fed up with you here.
Ok.  You see it first.
Yes, first of all it is fine.  I'll watch for two more hours.  Please
refund my money to me.
Ok.   A
call comes in two hours and then you are given an update.
Correct.
If you get your cancellation done then you
can share it with our team.  Our team
accepted the cancellation request.
Ok.  Ok.   Yes.  Anything else I can
help with?
No, that's enough.